https://www.beer-wine.com/privacy-policy/

Beer & Wine Hobby Logo
Search:
$0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Learn To Brew
Beer & Wine Hobby has a great collection of brewing learning materials so that you can become the brew master you have always wanted to become.
Learn How To Make Beer
Winemaking
Beer & Wine Hobby has a great collection of winemaking learning materials so that you can make the delicious home made wine you have always wanted to become
Learn How To Make Wine
Home Made Food
Beer & Wine Hobby has a great collection of food making learning materials to give you the knowledge you need to make the best homemade food possible.
Learn How To Make Food
Great Deals
Events
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We believe you deserve your privacy. Therefore, our privacy policy is simple - we keep your information for our mutual business purposes only. We never sell or give away your personal information.  If you have have questions about our policy, please contact us at bwhinfo@beer-wine.com
Privacy and Security of your Transactions
We use the industry-standard encryption protocol known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to keep all of your order, billing, and shipping information secure.
We have established a Secure Shopping Guarantee for every transaction that you make on the Beer & Wine Hobby website. Should any unauthorized charges appear on your credit card as a result of shopping on our website, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
About Us
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
About Beer & Wine Hobby
Beer & Wine Hobby is one of the oldest hobby suppliers in the USA. Our family-owned business provides the world's finest ingredients and equipment to make wine, craft beer, cheese, cordials and soft drinks. Our goal is to make shopping a very personal experience for you and provide expert advice every day, as we have since 1972.
Call and talk with us about your needs - we'd love to help you make whatever you want to create!
Learn more about us
Connect With Beer & Wine Hobby
How To Make Beer
How To Make Wine
How To Make Food
Blog
Beer Making Classes
Wine Making Classes
9am - 1pm
Closed all major holidays and 1 PM the day before Independence Day, Thanksgiving, Christmas & New Years
Company Info
+800-523-5423+781-933-8818
87 Andover Street, Unit 3Danvers, MA 01923
bwhinfo@beer-wine.com
Newsletter
Subscribe
Beer Equipment
Equipment Kits
Home Made Food
WARNING: If you are under 21 it is illegal for you to make or consume beer or wine in the United States. © 2016 Beer & Wine Hobby. All rights reserved.
To top
